[
    {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Task follows LIFO",
    "answer": "Stack"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Task follows FIFO",
    "answer": "Queue"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Language used for web page structure",
    "answer": "HTML"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Language used for styling web pages",
    "answer": "CSS"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Primary language for Android development",
    "answer": "Java"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Database language used for queries",
    "answer": "SQL"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "First search engine on the Internet",
    "answer": "Archie"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "The brain of the computer",
    "answer": "CPU"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Shortcut key to copy text",
    "answer": "Ctrl+C"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Shortcut key to paste text",
    "answer": "Ctrl+V"
  }
]